http://www.baen.com/privacy

The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.
Baen's Bar
Welcome!
Please login or sign up for a new account.
Remember me (not recommended for public devices.)
Reset
Welcome!
Sign up for a new account.
Privacy Statement for Baen Ebooks
Baen Ebooks has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website
http://www.baen.com/baenebooksWe use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, to make login more convenient (auto-login), and for other user benefits.
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
This site contains links to other sites. Baen Ebooks is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
You have to option to allow us to store your credit card numbers. This speeds up checkout. The numbers are stored encrypted and in any case are deleted after 3 months of non-use. Users may opt-out of having their card numbers stored; see the choice/opt-out section below.
We may use both "open-tracking" and "click-tracking" in our HTML newsletters (i.e. emails that contain text and images). Open-tracking allows us to find out how many people have viewed our email newsletters and click-tracking allows us to find out which links in the newsletter were clicked on. This helps us to refine and improve the editorial content of our newsletters, and to provide you with relevant information.
Public Forums—Baen's Bar
This site has links to forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Overall
Baen Ebooks does not sell or share personal information about its users to any third parties. Baen Ebooks may release general information, such as website traffic statistics, but never any information that would allow the third party to contact a Baen Ebooks user.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use SSL encryption to secure your credit transactions.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
Web based option: click here. Set the OK to Email to Yes or No. Check or uncheck the "Save My Credit Card Info" checkbox. Allowing us to save your credit card number will speed checkout in the future. Credit Card numbers are stored encrypted by Authorize.net.
You can send mail to the following postal address:
Baen EbooksP.O. Box 1188Wake Forest, NC 27588
Correct/Update
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
To change personal information in your profile, Login at www.baen.com, go to "Your Account", and change any information that you wish, including opting in or out of receiving Baen Ebooks newsletters by email.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or Baen Ebooks, please contact:
Baen EbooksP.O. Box 1188Wake Forest, NC 27588
baensupport@principledtechnologies.com
Baen Ebooks reserves the right to change or update these terms.
